Mohammed Abdelsalhyen Shereif

front-end developer

GitHub

Profile

I am a front-end developer with a passion for creating exceptional user experiences. I am dedicated to continuously learning and improving my skills whileworking effectively within team. I am interested in joining a strong development team where I can tackle Complex challenges and maximize user efficiency.

Education

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science

2019 - 2023

Minya university, Faculty of Computers and Information

work experience

MMTech Company 07/2024 – present

Front end developer

Minia ITI summer training Front End Development

08/2020 - 08/2020

Html | css | mySQL | PHP |WordPress

Skills

Projects

EcoShop complete e-commerce website application $\mathscr D$

Key Features

- Employ React Context API for managing state across the entire application effectively.
- Integrate Stripe for managing payments
- Manage content with Sanity
- Implement file-based routing with next js
- Implement hooks and refs for efficient state management.

Shareme social-media website application \mathscr{D}

Key Features

- Implement google auth for signup and login
- Manage content with Sanity and deal with content to upload, download and remove pictures
- Implement file-based routing with React-router
- Implement hooks and refs for efficient state management.

Souq-tech *∂*

Hitun &

Mazad *⊘*

My Portfolio ∂

Eng-System

Blood donation complete responsive website *⊗*

Elite responsive Education center website @

Languages

Arabic: Mother Tongue English